Justice runs in the family
Batman: Bad Blood is a science fiction, action,
animation film directed by Jay Oliva.
When Batman goes missing, it takes the entire Bat "family" - including Batwoman and Batwing - to keep
the peace in Gotham and unravel the mystery behind the Dark Knight's disappearance.
Batman / Bruce Wayne (voice), played by Jason O'Mara.
Batwoman / Kathy Kane (voice), played by Yvonne Strahovski.
Robin / Damian Wayne (voice), played by Stuart Allan.
Nightwing / Dick Grayson (voice), played by Sean Maher.
Talia al Ghul (voice), played by Morena Baccarin.
Black Mask / Firefly (voice), played by Steve Blum.
Batman: Bad Blood is a 2016 American animated superhero film which is the 25th film of the DC
Universe Animated Original Movies and the sixth film in the DC Animated Movie Universe.
It serves as a sequel to the 2015 film Batman vs.
The film was released on January 20, 2016, for iTunes and the Google
Play Store, and on DVD and Blu-ray on February 2.
While not a direct adaptation of a particular storyline, it derived from Grant
Morrison's run on Batman, primarily the Leviathan story arcs.
Jason O'Mara, Sean Maher, and Stuart Allan reprise their roles from the previous films as Batman, Nightwing, and Robin, with
Morena Baccarin returning from Son of Batman as Talia al Ghul, while Yvonne Strahovski joins as Batwoman.
The film explores themes of superhero, cartoon, based
on comic, super power, adult animation.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.